[
    {
        "question": "ويليام",
        "response": "ويليام"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايرين",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "همتارو",
        "response": "همتارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "الويفيا",
        "response": "الويفيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "رايلي",
        "response": "رايلي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ال",
        "response": "ال"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاو",
        "response": "لاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوريتشي",
        "response": "يوريتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتاتشي",
        "response": "ايتاتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "توبي",
        "response": "توبي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نوبارا",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاشيراما",
        "response": "هاشيراما"
    },
    {
        "question": "بوروتو",
        "response": "بوروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوسوب",
        "response": "يوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريم",
        "response": "ريم"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوتشيها شيسوي",
        "response": "اوتشيها شيسوي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيد",
        "response": "كيد"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكاسا",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "دانزو",
        "response": "دانزو"
    },
    {
        "question": "وينغ",
        "response": "وينغ"
    },
    {
        "question": "تينشيهان",
        "response": "تينشيهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "بيكوهان",
        "response": "بيكوهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "كازيكاجي",
        "response": "كازيكاجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيرايا",
        "response": "جيرايا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كازيكاجي",
        "response": "كازيكاجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوكومي",
        "response": "كوكومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غيو",
        "response": "غيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "تشيو",
        "response": "تشيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساسوري",
        "response": "ساسوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيزوكو",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميدوريا",
        "response": "ميدوريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيجي",
        "response": "نيجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليزا",
        "response": "ليزا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاغويا",
        "response": "كاغويا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هينا",
        "response": "هينا"
    },
    {
        "question": "الوكا",
        "response": "الوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيناتا",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "زينتسو",
        "response": "زينتسو"
    },
    {
        "question": "رينغوكو",
        "response": "رينغوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كورتا",
        "response": "كورتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيسوكا",
        "response": "هيسوكا"
    },
    {
       "question": "انوس",
        "response": "انوس"
    },
    {
       "question": "بياكوغان",
        "response": "بياكوغان"
    },
    {
       "question": "شوكو",
        "response": "شوكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ديكو",
        "response": "ديكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "يامي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {
       "question": "فانجانس",
        "response": "فانجانس"
    },
    {
       "question": "يوليوس",
        "response": "يوليوس"
    },
    {
       "question": "تسوموغو",
        "response": "تسوموغو"
    },
    {
       "question": "نانامي",
        "response": "نانامي"
    },
    {
       "question": "ايزن",
        "response": "ايزن"
    },
    {
       "question": "زاراكي",
        "response": "زاراكي"
    },
    {
       "question": "اوراهارا",
        "response": "اوراهارا"
    },
    {
       "question": "اينوي",
        "response": "اينوي"
    },
    {
       "question": "غوهان",
        "response": "غوهان"
    },
    {
       "question": "كيريلين",
        "response": "كيريلين"
    },
    {
       "question": "هيناتسورو",
        "response": "هيناتسورو"
    },
    {
       "question": "ريتشيل",
       "response": "ريتشيل"
}
]
